I'm sorry...
I'm really sorry...
but even if you hate me,
even if you hate me a lot,
can't you stay with me?
Let go.
I feel like every string that kept me
connected to the world has been detached.
It's really ridiculous...
it really makes no sense...
but I'm always worried about that kid.
I'm really going crazy.
It's really unbelievable...
but I think I like that kid.
What in the world am I going
to do with you?
So I want to hurry and get over this.
I have to get over it.
I can do it.
-=Episode 12=-
"An Exercise In Memory"
Hey.
Didn't you say I didn't like you
because you were messy?
Yeah. I cleaned because you always
nagged me.
I don't remember it, but it feels
more comfortable than my own house.
It's only until you get back your memory.
Once you get your memory,
don't come back here again.
And don't come looking for me again.
Hurry and answer me.
Okay.
You know you're having another
trial soon, right?
This time, I can't be your attorney,
because the trial won't be in the Yeonju
district, but in the Seoul High Court.
I'm not sure if you'll be found
innocent this time.
Yes.
That's why...
you have to do whatever you can
to find your memories.
Think of it as a jigsaw puzzle and put
together as many pieces as you can.
Yes, I will.
Why are your eyes so red?
Since the verdict, I haven't been able
to sleep. I think it's insomnia.
Really?
You used to fall asleep in a second.
How can you have insomnia?
Is it from stress?
Hey, are you asleep?
I thought you had insomnia.
Hey, go in your room and sleep.
But what lawyer is going to
defend him this time?
Lawyer Cha knows this case.
So if Lawyer Cha would do it,
that would be the best.
Should I try and ask him?
I'm crazy, crazy.
How can I be so shameless?
Jang Hye Seong, you're really low.
A total shit!
That hurts!
But should I do it anyway?
How long did I sleep?
There's curry in the fridge.
Heat it up and eat it.
That's why... you have to do whatever
you can to find your memories.
Think of it as a jigsaw puzzle and put
together as many pieces as you can.
With Min Jun Guk at the fishery.
Traffic accident alone on the road.
With Lawyer Jang at the aquarium.
No. This is really shameless,
even for me.
But Lawyer Cha is the one I trust
the most.
No. People really can't be like this.
But if Su Ha gets stuck with a weirdo
lawyer, then what?
=What are you doing now?=
Lawyer Cha!
Do you have something to say to me?
No. Nothing.
Tell me.
No. I can't.
You want to ask me to defend
Pak Su Ha, right?
That must be it.
No.
I thought about it a tiny bit,
but I gave up.
I'm not quite that shameless.
I feel bad about it, so I can't.
I won't.
I'll do it. Defend Pak Su Ha.
What?
I said I'll be his attorney.
So, I will let Lawyer Jang feel bad for me.
I will let you feel burdened.
That way, you can get rid of your
ridiculous feelings for him quicker, right?
Lawyer Cha... I...
I will work very hard as his lawyer,
so that you will feel very burdened by it.
Starting from now, it's my case,
so keep your hands out of it.
Okay?
What?
Okay.
Aja! Aja! Fighting!
I feel like I'm going to die.
You see that, right?
Pak Su Ha is telling an outrageous lie
that he can read minds.
Can we say that Pak Su Ha's allegations
are actually consistent and accurate?
Do you have any other evidence,
or maybe a witness?
Is there a problem?
I...
I'm a witness for this murder case.
I'm Jang Hye Seong.
Will I be able to win... this fight?
Thank you.
If it wasn't for you today,
there would have been no one to
sign me out.
I brought the car.
I'll drop you off. Let's go.
Yes.
Isn't this car a little wild?
People like me not being compatible
with sports cars,
that's an idea you need to throw out.
It's not that.
Will this car even run?
Of course!
It hasn't broken down in the last 16 years.
Get in.
The world has changed a lot.
Don't worry.
You'll catch up before you know it.
I'm not so sure.
I don't know if I'll have time to catch up.
If I can just see my daughter before I die,
I won't have any regrets.
What's that?
This was in my bag 26 years ago
when I was arrested.
It was a gift for Ga Eun.
I'm sorry.
For what?
Just for everything.
What are you talking about?
I'm very grateful to you.
You are the only person who
believed in me.
Is Prosecutor Seo inside?
No. She's on an investigation in
Gapyeong right now.
Investigation? What investigation?
Something regarding Min Jun Guk.
Min Jun Guk?
But why would Prosecutor Seo
investigate a dead person?
I know. But it seems like she thinks
he might not be dead.
What?
I already told you, he's not here!
Really?
Then, what about these?
He's not there, Prosecutor!
How long are you going to keep
doing this?
Of course, until we find him.
There must be a reason that person
didn't make the report himself.
But speaking of that person,
how were his hands?
What?
I said, his hands. Hands. How were they?
Well, they were fine!
Fine?
Right. They were fine.
What else would they be?
You're home very late.
Have you eaten?
If you haven't, we can eat...
I've already eaten.
Go see Lawyer Cha tomorrow.
He's going to be your lawyer for
the second trial.
This is Lawyer Cha's contact details.
You don't need to worry about money.
He won't charge you.
Did you perhaps ask him to do it?
Is that important?
Yes, it's important.
Right. I did ask him.
I'm sure you're already aware.
Do you think anybody else
is as good as Lawyer Cha?
Although I do feel very sorry
and obligated to him for it,
I can't be involved in your case anymore.
There's no other choice
except for Lawyer Cha.
You know?
Okay. I'll go see him tomorrow.
Go talk to him.
Be polite.
-=Law Office of Cha Gwan Wu=-
I'm always worried about him.
What's wrong with me?
I'm dying of hunger.
-=Law Office of Cha Gwan Wu=-
Over here!
Do you want something to drink?
I'll buy it myself.
Fine.
During this time, have you
remembered anything else?
Yes. First I remembered being at
the fishery with Min Jun Guk.
But what we talked about or what we did,
I can't remember.
You're sure you didn't fight with him?
Yes. I don't remember that.
You still haven't remembered anything
that seems helpful.
Is there anything else?
After I saw Min Jun Guk, I think I was
in a traffic accident.
I think I remember it was on a road
near the dam.
I was hit by a blue truck there.
A blue truck?
The 1-ton type?
Yes, I think so.
We need to find out about that.
Do you possibly remember the
license plate?
So then I should look into the accident
reports at nearby police stations.
And hospital records.
Thank you for taking this case.
You don't need to thank me.
I'm only doing it because Lawyer Jang
asked me.
How much is your fee?
You're not a public defender now,
but a private lawyer,
so there must be a fee, right?
Kid, when I was a public defender,
I was free.
But as a private lawyer,
I'm very expensive.
If I say I'm doing it for free,
then you should just accept it.
Put your energy into getting back
your memory.
Please don't treat me like a child.
I will pay your fee, so just tell me.
Take Lawyer Jang out of this situation.
My father left me a house and
insurance money,
so I can pay your fee.
So, please don't burden Lawyer Jang
with any of this.
Aren't you the one who is
burdening Lawyer Jang?
Su Ha, you should stop playing an adult,
and start acting like a real one.
Wearing a suit doesn't make you an adult.
Right now, you're just a high school
dropout and a murder suspect,
with no memory and no future.
That's why Lawyer Jang has taken you in.
Don't mistake that for something else.
And also, I went easy on you a year ago
because you were young,
but not anymore.
When you get back your memories
and you get a not guilty verdict,
don't burden Lawyer Jang any further,
and move out of that house.
Like you said,
you're not a child anymore.
I'm not any better.
Because I feel so desperate,
I have really hit rock bottom.
Lawyer Shin.
This Shim Wo Dal case,
since she stabbed her husband because
he always beat her,
can't we argue this as a self-defense case?
Lawyer Shin!
Are you asleep?
Just give it up.
He's been doing that lately.
Why?
He's way past menopause, isn't he?
I can hear you.
If you heard what I said,
then please tell me.
This case... Could we win if we go
with reasonable self-defense?
In this situation,
I can scarcely remember any that
won going with self-defense.
It's better just to plead guilty.
Then you can argue for
a reduced sentence.
But the defendant said she will
take responsibility,
and she wants me defend her
as not guilty.
Then convince her somehow.
You're the lawyer.
I understand.
-=Appeal=-
But speaking of that person,
how were his hands?
What?
I said, his hands. Hands. How were they?
Well, they were fine!
Fine?
Right. They were fine.
What else would they be?
Chief Yang.
I want to ask you something.
How are Bo Hee's hands?
Her hands?
Pale and very pretty.
Why?
Bo Hee, how are Chief Yang's hands?
Kind of thick and rough.
Prosecutor Seo, have you finished
writing the appeal for the Pak Su Ha case?
Ju seonbae.
What do you think of my hands?
Your hands? I don't know...
your fingers are long and thin,
aren't they?
Right.
Whenever I ask anyone about hands,
people describe them as
pale, pretty, thick, rough...
they answer like that.
But saying a hand is fine...
that's a strange answer, isn't it?
It's fine?
Someone answered like that?
Yes. The person who reported Pak Su Ha,
Mun Seong Nam.
I asked her about the hands on the
person who told her about Pak Su Ha,
But she answered that they were "fine."
Isn't that strange?
Could it be... Min Jun Guk?
If it's like what Pak Su Ha's side claims,
and Min Jun Guk doesn't have a left hand...
And if that lady is trying to protect
Min Jun Guk because he gave her the tip...
She would answer that his hands
were fine, right?
Awesome!
No, wait...
If he were still alive,
where has he been that we haven't
found a trace of him?
That's because we haven't really
been looking for him.
Starting from now, I want to
seriously look for him.
Chief Yang.
Please serve Mun Seong Nam
with a witness summons.
Okay.
Hyeong, do we have that kind of
relationship?
You just need to take a look at
the records.
How much did I help you out
when I was a police officer?
=Ah, hyeong!=
Stop your damn whining.
What do you want to know?
Last year on July 22nd or 23rd,
do you have any reports regarding
traffic accidents?
=Check for anything involving hitting
a person, or crashing into an object.=
Last year, July 22nd or 23rd...
2 incidents of a car hitting a person,
3 incidents of a car crashing into an object.
Were any of them involving a blue truck?
A 1-ton truck.
Yeah, there's one.
It occurred on a side road by the dam.
Who was driving the truck?
It says Gim Gi Ho.
Gim Gi Ho?
His address is...
Ganghwa Island.
That's right.
=How did you know?=
Thank you, hyeong.
Next time you have legal problems,
just call me.
I'll take care of you for free.
Gim Gi Ho.
Su Ha!
Why are you in such a hurry?
From now on, don't call us here
as a set. I don't like it.
I don't like it either,
even more.
Why did you call today?
Did you get back your memory?
No. So I think I need you guys
to help me.
How can we help with that?
Tell me everything you know about
Lawyer Jang and me.
What's that? Are you interested
in the police academy?
No. I was just looking at it.
Dude, don't even look at it.
It's really hard to get in there.
Your case isn't even closed yet.
If you get found guilty, you won't be
able to get in there in a million years.
Is that right?
No, Su Ha can do it.
You were a really good student
in high school.
Really? That's surprising.
Su Ha, if you became a police officer,
you'd look really handsome.
I love men in uniforms.
Our car center also has uniforms,
you know.
It feels too awkward to
eat with Su Ha.
Should I just go eat by myself?
That's mine.
What are you doing?
You're here?
Lawyer Jang, why in the world
do you do this?
It only confuses me and makes me dizzy.
Really? When I go in there,
it makes everything clear for me.
I guess it doesn't work when
you're older.
Why do you have to mention age?
Has something been bothering you lately?
It's not puberty, so what's going on?
Do you have to go through puberty
for something to bother you?
Oh, there's a new street diner.
When did that come?
Are you going there?
That's right!
I thought you didn't drink anything
except wine.
Lawyer Jang, just go your own way
and keep your mouth closed!
Let's go together!
There must be something in the air today.
I just ran into Prosecutor Seo in front
of the courthouse and came over here.
Lawyer Shin and Lawyer Jang
came, too.
Have a seat.
Sure.
All right.
Sit here.
Prosecutor Seo can really drink!
She's had 2 bottles of soju and is still sober.
Owner, 3 bottles of soju, please!
Okay!
What? 3 bottles?
Are you going to drink all that?
You should know that I can
handle alcohol well.
You can hold your alcohol?
You see? I'm totally fine, right?
Yes, you're just great.
Prosecutor Seo, are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
But it's kind of hot in here.
A sesame leaf and now lettuce.
That's quite a sight.
Lawyer Jang, whenever I see you,
there's something I wonder about.
Ask me.
When you were taking the public
defender interview,
didn't you say you regretted going
into that courtroom to testify?
Yes, I regret it.
Why do you regret it?
In fact, the reason I went to testify
was just to show that awful girl
and her father
that I was right, and that girl was wrong.
1. 2. 3.
That's why I opened the door and went in.
But I never got anything from that.
Why haven't you gotten anything?
Because you testified, you caught a
criminal and upheld justice.
Justice? That's bullshit.
That stupid cellphone.
The cellphone?
Pak Su Ha's testimony has lost credibility.
Didn't you just hear what he said
about reading minds?
Right now, he is lying to make sure
this defendant is found guilty.
It would be a little difficult to
call her as a witness.
I have a photo here.
I took a picture of that man using
the metal pipe.
Wouldn't that be called evidence?
But because of that cellphone,
everything was for nothing.
Everything was for nothing? Why?
You must have been scared,
but you did very well.
If not for you, this would have been
called just a simple traffic accident.
Did you see the photo?
I saw it. There was nothing there.
The lie I told... will it be okay?
Of course. You did well.
When they're about to walk away in
front of you, how can we just do nothing?
Even if you have to shoot them with
a blank, you have to catch them.
A blank?
You did a good job today. I'll let you
know when the verdict comes out.
Did you know?
There was another witness.
Who is it?
Do Yeon.
What? Do Yeon?
At the time that it happened,
she was with me.
So she was supposed to come here
today with me,
but she ran away.
Do Yeon is a liar.
About today, and about the fireworks too.
I know. Do Yeon did tell a lie.
But because of that, I knew you
were the culprit.
Ajussi! That's...
I believe something like that
isn't really a lie,
whether it was Do Yeon,
or what you did just now.
If it's not a lie, then what is it?
A blank.
Firing a blank to catch a criminal.
I felt it was really unfair.
For the sake of my honor,
just to prove I was right...
I ended up risking my life.
But I never got anything for it.
Only...
a sworn enemy to haunt my life.
How about it?
You think I should regret it, right?
Regret?
Was your regret as much as mine?
I also have regrets.
For over 11 years, I have been
regretting that I didn't open that door.
Then, Prosecutor Seo is that awful...
You're that girl?
Do you know why I hated you so much?
1.
2.
3.
Because you witnessed the most
pathetic moment of my entire life.
Every time I see you, I think of
that damn moment.
Do you have any idea how much
I have regretted that?
I always wished I could go back to
that moment and be a witness.
That moment, even now,
I still regret it.
I wanted to somehow make up
for that moment.
From that day on, I gave up my art
and cut myself off from my friends.
I did nothing but study so that I
could become a prosecutor.
I wanted you and father to see...
that I wasn't me that day.
That I made a mistake.
I've been doing everything for
11 years just to justify that.
Do you know that?
For 11 years!
I'll be leaving first.
Prosecutor Seo.
Prosecutor Seo, you can't just
leave like this!
I'll be leaving too.
Lawyer Jang! Lawyer Jang!
You're just leaving...
Lawyer Jang! What will we do when the
people who drank the most leave?
Pay your bill!
When I met you here, I was curious.
Such a big-time prosecutor,
why did I,
just a public defender,
have to run into you?
Why did fate have such a sick sense of
humor to make us meet like this?
That's an interesting friendship.
Those two people.
I know what you mean. I didn't know
they had that kind of history.
But to actually meet each other again as
prosecutor and lawyer.
No kidding. Life is full of coincidences,
right?
Like they say, coincidences are
carefully planned by heaven.
If heaven arranges for two people
to see each other again,
don't you think there must be a reason
they needed to come together again?
Right now, you're just a high school
dropout
and a murder suspect,
with no memory and no future.
That's why Lawyer Jang has taken you in.
Don't mistake that for something else.
Why are those shoes there?
These are Lawyer Jang's clothes.
Aren't you the one who is
burdening Lawyer Jang?
Seo Do Yeon, you bad girl.
What is this scar?
I think you drank a lot last night.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Can't you just not drink? It doesn't
seem like you hold it very well.
My drinking ability is well known.
I've always come back home to sleep
and never caused any trouble.
So, you don't need to worry.
Aren't you going to eat today?
I made bean sprout soup.
I have some things to do early today.
Aren't you just avoiding me?
No, I'm not.
What are you doing?
I have something to ask you.
What's that?
I saw the scar on your side.
What's that from?
If he finds that out, it will be
painful for him.
When did you see that?
It's just from an appendix surgery.
An appendix surgery?
Yes, an appendix surgery. Okay?
One more thing.
Whatever I have to do, I'm going to get
acquitted. After I get acquitted,
I'm going to college.
Then I will make friends and get a
part-time job and work hard.
I won't be a burden to you,
so you don't have to worry.
I will do my best.
Really? That sounds pretty good.
I won't nag you anymore. I won't annoy
you or make things hard for you.
That sounds pretty good, too.
So, don't avoid me.
Don't come home late to avoid me,
or skip your meals.
And don't hate me.
It's the same bag.
She's so damn annoying.
Justice? That's bullshit.
That stupid cellphone.
I said that? Damn, damn, damn!
I also have regrets.
For over 11 years, I have been
regretting that I didn't open that door.
Darn it.
Do you remember anything yesterday
after drinking?
Not a thing.
What about you?
Me either. Not a thing.
So now that Prosecutor Seo
is calling me in as a witness.
Aigoo. She's really stubborn.
Don't worry. When I go,
I won't say a word about you.
When do they want you to come?
Tomorrow.
I guess I'll have to close the
business tomorrow.
Oh, Right. Here are a few peaches
you can take with you to eat.
Thank you, Boss.
What's this?
I saw on your resume that
today is your birthday.
So I made you some seaweed soup
and some side dishes.
Take it home and eat it.
You should already know what I'm
going to do.
Aren't you afraid?
I'm not afraid. I only feel that you're
worthless and I pity you.
Living all those years only hating others.
Your life must have been a living hell.
What are you thinking about?
I'm just... thinking about what to do.
Whether I should just give up here,
or keep going to the end.
Are you traveling?
Traveling? Yes, I'm traveling.
But now that I'm here,
this spot is pretty good.
Whether I should just stop here...
that's what I'm wondering.
But since you said you're traveling,
shouldn't you go all the way to the end?
Should I? You think so too, Boss?
If you're traveling, then you
need to finish it.
That's right.
I have to go to the end.
I think so, too.
Truck?
After I saw Min Jun Guk, I think I was
in a traffic accident.
I think I remember it was on a road
near the dam.
I was hit by a blue truck there.
Bingo.
Who are you?
Hello, Elder.
I have a few things I need to ask
you about.
That's sweet and really tasty.
What is it you want to ask me?
You know Pak Su Ha, right?
No...
You called him Lee Seun Uk, right?
Why this again? I already told the
police and the prosecutor.
They already investigated me.
It's because now we have some new
information that we didn't know before.
What's that?
Elder, by any chance, one year ago...
did you with that truck...
Pak Su Ha... No...
hit Lee Seun Uk with it?
Who said that?
Did Seun Uk say that?
Does he remember that now?
Yes. He said he remembered that.
So, you can tell me the truth about it now.
Why did you hide him after the accident?
After you hit a person, you reported
that you ran into an object.
Actually, I was planning to report the
accident and take responsibility.
Truly!
But that person told me not to do it.
That since that child had lost his memory,
I just shouldn't tell anyone.
Who was that person?
- Hello?
- =Prosecutor, there's a problem!=
The witness who we summoned,
Mun Seong Nam...
Last night, she was killed in a car accident.
What?
What happened?
They said it's drunk driving.
She was coming this way from
over there,
and then she went over the bridge.
She died instantly of a broken neck.
It was drunk driving?
Yes. Her blood alcohol level was 0.19%.
She was extremely drunk.
Have you looked at the CCTV?
Yes.
But it was out of order.
Not only that, it broke only
1 hour before the accident.
A witness against Min Jun Guk,
who just received a summons,
suddenly dies of a drunk driving accident?
In addition, the CCTV malfunctions
1 hour before the accident.
Do you think all that is coincidence?
It's not coincidence. No way.
Starting now, we're going to say
Min Jun Guk is still alive.
Put Min Jun Guk on the wanted list.
Yes.
What is that scar?
This looks a lot like her scar.
This... this...
what's going on?
That can't be.
Why would you?
Why? Why did you?
Hey, Rice Pot.
How many times did I tell you?
If you kill that man...
you won't be the victim any more,
but the murderer.
Don't say a word about this, ever.
You didn't stab me.
If you ever say anything else,
I'm never... going to see you again.
I'm a witness for this murder case.
I'm Jang Hye Seong.
I will... protect you.
Uncle! I'm over here!
It hurts!
I can read other people's minds.
Stop!
You think your father was a good man,
don't you?
Just as I killed your father,
your father killed my wife.
No.
It's not possible.
No. It's not possible.
You think your father was a good man,
don't you?
That's enough! Shut up!
Quit lying!
You know that I'm not lying to you
right now.
Stop. Please.
Your father...
with that treacherous tongue,
he killed my wife.
The one who started all of this wasn't me!
It was your father!
Shut up! Shut up!
Right.
I know you want to kill me right now.
Kill me. Go ahead and kill me.
How are you any different than
I was 11 years ago?
I will never do the thing you're
worried about.
I promise you I'll keep my word.
Please trust me.
I am different.
I won't live as a beast like you.
Ever.
Stop! Pak Su Ha!
Stop right there!
Father, please tell me it isn't true.
Father! Father!
Kid, how can you just run out like that?
If I show weakness I'll be at a
disadvantage.
I need to come on tough.
Are you trying to get killed?
Are you blind?
Why was he like that?
That driver was at fault.
- This is a sidewalk.
- Why didn't he say anything?
- Should we call the police?
- What's going on?
- Really annoying.
- Why are there so many people?
Lawyer Jang! Lawyer Jang!
Min Jun Guk is still alive!
Yes. I just heard that.
Prosecutor Seo, why are you here?
I also confirmed that fact,
that Min Jun Guk is still alive.
How did you find out?
The grandpa that was hiding
Pak Su Ha for that year,
he was drinking and driving, and hit
Pak Su Ha with his truck a year ago.
Is that why he kept him?
Just to hide his drunk driving accident?
He originally wanted to go to the police,
but someone prevented him.
He told him to keep it buried,
because Pak Su Ha had lost his memory.
Don't tell me...
It was Min Jun Guk.
He said Min Jun Guk was already
missing his left hand.
My gosh, then Min Jun Guk
really did stage all of this.
Where is Min Jun Guk now?
We're not sure. We have issued
an arrest warrant for him.
I've told the police in the region to
canvass the area for him.
I'm checking into a retaliation crime
prevention strategies,
so don't be scared.
What about Su Ha?
What about Su Ha's appeal case?
What?
Since Min Jun Guk is still alive,
Su Ha's case should be dropped,
shouldn't it?
Hey. Is that important in this
situation right now?
Yes, it comes first.
You'll drop the charges, right?
Yes, I will.
Thanks.
I'm going out for a while.
Where are you going?
To tell Su Ha.
The one who started all of this wasn't me!
It was your father!
That's what it was...
the memory I wanted to erase.
But erasing it won't make it go away.
What should I do with you?
If you knew this, you'd hate me more.
If you knew Min Jun Guk was still alive,
how scared would you be?
Min Jun Guk is still alive.
Su Ha didn't kill him.
That guy really did keep his
promise to me.
Hello?
Hey, where are you now? At home?
No, I came out for a while.
Min Jun Guk is alive.  Seo Do Yeon
and Lawyer Cha found out.
Okay.
What's that reaction?
I said Min Jun Guk is alive!
You're now completely innocent and
you won't have another trial!
That person is alive.
That means that you're in danger.
Hey, Rice Pot!
We'll deal with that later.
Seo Do Yeon said she's going to drop
the charges against you. I heard it myself.
So, you're not a defendant anymore...
Hey!
You're the rice pot.
Your life is being threatened again.
How can me being innocent come first?
How can you think that?
Thanks... for keeping your promise.
~ It's like you're in my distant memory ~
~ waiting there for me ~
~ You beckon to me like a whisper ~
~ Deep in my heart,  ~
deep in my soul,
~ your voice deep within me, ~
~ I hear it ~